ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION: 15 - A NEW FAMILY MEMBER
The dog attacked him! I can kill him!
Explode, you pig!
What?
The Minister threw the bomb
into the river?
Get off of me for a bit.
I'll let you go free in a little while,
so stay in there for now.
That old man couldn't have…
Wait, who is that?
Why is a different person here instead?
Did I make a mistake? Damn it!
I got his number plate. He won't be
able to run away in that conspicuous car.
You guys' plan has failed.
Anya!
Did she go back to
the first pet shop we were at?
It would disastrous
if she runs into those terrorists again.
I have to catch up to her!
That guy! You tried to take Anya!
I won't let you go this time!
What? Did she fall from the sky?
Get out of the way!
Hello, is this the police?
I found a terrorist
in a car accident
in the back alley of Kitamachi Park.
Please come get him right away.
No, I'm the housewife that called earlier.
Well, goodbye.
Anya!
Anyways, I guess everything is
settled now.
It sure was an unlucky day.
Thankfully it ended
without causing a big uproar.
We'll just wait for the eastern government
to make it seem like it never happened.
We'll pass these dogs
over to them as well.
We're not obligated to do that. We'll hide
them here, and report it to the top.
It seems like we'll need to
investigate this more deeply.
Well, I'll be going now.
I must return to my family
as soon as possible.
Good work.
What are you two doing here?
Weren't you at the adoption event?
I came back because I was worried
about you in the bathroom.
I chased after her
because I was worried about Anya.
And what's with this dog?
…So, that's what happened.
That's why we were too busy
to be looking for a pet.
I can't believe these two
were caught up in that case.
I'm sorry you had to go through that
while I was in the restroom.
No! I think you got sick
because of the breakfast I made!
I'm the one who's sorry!
And you!
I'm always telling you not to go off
on your own because it's dangerous!
I'm sorry!
You're not hurt?
It's because Doggie protected me.
This dog was also used as an experiment
for Project Apple, huh?
If that's the case,
I can't let him go free.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
Excuse me.
I'm from the State Security Service.
We're investigating the case at Central.
May we ask you guys some questions?
I see.
Then that dog was most likely trained
by those terrorists as well.
We will take that dog with us.
Thank you very much.
We will not be disclosing
this incident due to the situation
between the east and west,
so please keep this a secret.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Now that this is settled,
let's go back to looking for a dog.
Good idea. Let's go, Anya.
I don't want to! Anya wants this doggie!
What are you saying?
Anya wants to keep this doggie.
No, you can't. That's the bad guy's dog--
He saved Anya!
But you said that you wanted a small dog.
I want this doggie! I want a big one!
Don't kick up a fuss.
If I can't keep this doggie, I'm going to
rebel and stop going to school!
What are you saying?
Why bring the school into this?
It's okay, don't worry.
-It's okay, Anya.
-Anya!
Fine. I'll allow it.
Handler-- I mean, Ma'am.
Is it really okay?
One dog going missing won't cause
any problems.
All the terrorists were arrested,
and this dog is harmless.
Wait…
Operation Strix will be in a crisis
unless we do this.
-We have no other choice.
-I know, but still…
Place him under your supervision
and manage him closely.
We have the other dogs for
our investigative research, so no worries.
You want to increase my workload?
There were lots of other dogs,
but will they be bullied
at the police station?
Don't worry, little girl.
We'll treat the dogs with respect.
We'll prepare soft beds
and warm food for them as well.
We believe that these dogs
experienced a lot of hardships until now.
So make sure you
treat this dog nicely
and look after him with care.
It's a promise, okay?
Okay.
Thank you, important lady.
She's a good kid.
You don't know my hardships.
I actually do.
I used to have a daughter that age.
Good for you, Anya. You too, Doggie.
I'm just glad that there is peace today.
I agree.
We will take him overnight to examine him
and check for any health issues.
If there are no issues, we will drop
him off at your house tomorrow.
I understand.
Shall we head home?
Yes, let's!
I'm a little tired because it was
such a long day.
The field trip isn't over until you get
back home. We can't let our guard down.
Did you learn that at school?
This is not a field trip.
Don't you worry, Anya.
The case is closed now.
Today, I took down some bad guys
and secretly protected the peace
of this country.
Father was able to stop the bombing
thanks to Anya.
Anya saved the world.
We barely managed to avoid
the tension between the east and west,
but this is bad for my health.
My stomach hurts.
Onto the next news story.
I wonder when Doggie is coming.
…Two car accidents…
Calm down. He'll be coming soon.
You're blocking the TV.
Good evening.
Doggie!
I'll leave him in your care.
He looks like he's saying, "Where am I?"
Welcome to Anya's house, Doggie!
Starting today, this is your house!
We should give him a name.
A name?
Number eight. Get out.
It's time for your drugs.
Hey! Stay still!
Here's your food. Be grateful and eat it.
Raise the voltage.
It's too high!
It doesn't matter. There are many
replacements if this one dies.
I wonder what's wrong.
Are you nervous? Do you want some snacks?
Don't be shy. You're a part of
the Forger family now.
The summit that began last night
resumed today for the second day,
and the negotiation regarding
disarmament is proceeding smoothly…
I participated in catching the bad guys
but Anya can't get a star?
That's right. In order to prevent
trouble between east and west
that incident has to be kept a secret.
Don't talk about it at school either.
Otherwise you'll get caught by the police,
and you'll never come home again.
Even though we saved the world together.
Anya, it's time to go.
If I can't get the star, then…
I have to go with
the "Friendship Strategy"!
I'll go to the second son's house to help
Father accomplish his mission.
What? You got a dog?
Yup.
It's a competition to see
whose dog is bigger! Bring him over!
Anya will save the world many times over.
Just you wait.
Huh?
Good morning, Anya.
Good morning.
Oh, I'm glad to see that she's over
the "Starlight" phase.
Listen, Becky.
A dog has come to Anya's house.
What? Really? What kind of dog?
What breed is it?
Huh? It's a white one.
How old is it?
Don't know. It's big.
I wonder which is cuter?
Your dog, or my Wiesel.
I hope they can play together.
This method might work!
Can I go over to your house sometime--
Hey!
What do you want?
Anya has a dog.
So what?
The world has come to an end.
You dismissed a commoner
with just one word.
-Just as I expected of you, Damian.
-Huh?
-Did I say something that mean?
-You've gone beyond my expectations.
Her dog is probably some
dirty old mongrel.
What's the dog's name?
Name?
Yeah.
I guess I'll let you tell me that much.
Dog.
You're not qualified to own a dog.
I wasted my time talking with you.
Oh no!
What? How to choose a name?
You can name it after cute food,
or a flower.
Food? Peanuts.
But your dog is big, right?
Wouldn't peanuts sound weird?
It's important to think about his
appearance too.
His appearance… White hair.
What?
It might be better to have your
mom or dad decide on the name.
Huh?
Anya doesn't have the talent for this?
Father. Mother. Anya is back.
Welcome back.
Look at that. They've become fast friends.
Help me. He's going to eat me!
Should we take him out for a walk?
A walk!
There's a dog park near the library.
Dog goes bark, bark
Father, Anya wants to pull on
that string too.
You're too young for this.
You'll get dragged.
Although he's been trained,
we need to teach him manners.
You'll have to learn
and remember new things too.
How to feed, praise, and discipline him.
Among many other things.
You must be determined to
care for him responsibly until the end.
Yes, sir.
By the way, did you decide on his name?
Anya's naming skill is pretty hopeless.
What? Oh, I see…
It should be a simple name that's easy
to say and easy for the dog to understand.
I hear dogs have a hard time
differentiating consonants,
so you should construct a name
that makes the vowels stand out.
Especially, A, U, and O.
It's so hard.
Can't differentiate the consonants?
So you want to suffer somehow?
Should we slash the shin?
What? You can't differentiate them?
Let's name him after we figure out
his personality.
It's a dog park!
Hey!
Run around, Doggie!
Otherwise, it'll become an Anya park
instead of a dog park.
Ready, Leon? Go catch it.
All right. Let's do that, Doggie.
Go get it!
Do we have to decide on your name first?
Excuse me.
What's your dog's name?
How did you choose that name?
Tell me your secret.
Don't go too far.
Your name is Lucky Vanilla Princess III.
Then Atomic Angel Charlie Shogun.
Anya looks like she's having fun.
Determined to care for him
responsibly until the end.
I have no right to say that.
Once my mission ends,
the Forger family will be dismissed.
My time with these two will end.
Of course I plan to tie up loose ends
the best I can,
but this terrorist incident reminded me
that the peace between the east
and west is nothing but show.
We must work to end this cold war
as quickly as possible.
It's for a better future.
Hey, we should start heading back.
It's time to study.
No way.
Oh? Wait.
Oh no!
Anya lost her gloves. Where are they?
Did you drop them somewhere?
They were Anya's favorites.
I don't see them anywhere.
Those are Anya's gloves.
Give it back.
I found this treasure so it's mine!
Hey there! What are you doing to my baby!
Where did that mutt come from?
That was scary, huh?
Thank you, Doggie.
Here's your stomach warmer
that the evil organization stole.
I retrieved it for you, Princess Honey.
Thank you, Bondman!
This is an important item
that I got from my late mother!
You're like Bondman.
You retrieved this for me.
Come to think of it,
you have gloves on too.
What's wrong?
Father! I decided on a name for Doggie!
Doggie's name will be Bond.
Bond from Bondman, huh?
That's not bad.
That tickles.
It seems like he likes it.
The collar is perfect too!
All right, Bond. I'm giving you
your very first mission.
Finish this bowl of dog food.
Don't overfeed him.
It's neither good nor bad.
Oh, you have to pee. Come follow me, Bond.
Listen carefully. This is your bathroom.
If you do your business anywhere else,
our clean freak mother might get mad.
Do your business with care
so as not to get killed.
It was poop. It stinks.
All right, Bond. Now it's time to
watch anime.
I'll teach you where your name comes from.
Hey, I told you that it's time to study.
Get ready by the time I get out of
the bath.
Those two…
Loid, come here.
Look at that.
What is it?
They got exhausted from playing,
and fell asleep.
What is she, an angel?
I guess I'll give her a break today.
Yes, let's do that.
MISSION: 16 - YOR'S KITCHEN/
THE GREAT ROMANCE SCHEME FOR THE INFORMANT
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita